LAURA ASHLEIGH



Professional Skills:

JavaScript and ReactJS HTML5 and CSS3 Java, C#, Python and SQL Analyse software requirements Create technical documentation **UI** Design UX Mobile applications Testing and debugging GitHub and GitFlow

Personal Skills:

Reliable and professional Team player Fast learner Motivated Communication Interpersonal skills Organisation Time management Flexibility

Email: lauraann.ashleigh@gmail.com

Phone: 0422236518

Address: Manly, Sydney 2095

ABOUT ME

I am currently working as a Metadata Engineer on a metadata management system for IAG. I am the sole front-end developer of this system, working predominantly with React. Previously, I was a Primary Teacher for 5 years, however was looking to broaden my horizons and take the next step in my career with my computer programming knowledge. My passion for learning inspires me to continually gain new skills. My next goal is to further develop my web development skills and nurture my curiosity and passion for coding. Visit my profile to learn more about me and access my projects.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2020 - Metadata Engineer at IAG 2019-2020 - Intern Developer at IAG 2017-2018 - Full-time Classroom Teacher on Years 5 and 6 at St. Kieran's Manly Vale 2014-2016 – Full-time Classroom Teacher on Year 4 at St. Joseph's Narrabeen

EDUCATION

Continuous self-directed learning around web development 2019 - CertIV in Programming, Open Colleges Australia 2016 - Graduate Certificate in Theology, Broken Bay Institute 2013 – Bachelor of Teaching (Primary)/Bachelor of Arts, University of Newcastle, GPA: 6.4 / 7 2008 - High School Certificate, St. Francis Xavier's College, Hamilton, UAI/ATAR: 92.5